hi thank you everyone for coming to our
嗨，谢谢大家参加我们的活动
come elections compare talk and it's a
来选举比较谈话，这是一个
interactive session if you don't like to
互动会话（如果您不喜欢）
ask questions please do otherwise just
问问题，否则就做
speaking long enough that we can repeat
说话时间足够长，我们可以重复
it back is being retype it okay and I'll
回来重新输入就可以了，我会
briefly talk about our guests our
简短地谈论我们的客人
speakers first you know for medical
首先要了解医疗的演讲者
order don't not please
订购请不要
hey so I welcome everyone my name is
嘿，所以欢迎大家，我叫
Donald robb
唐纳德·罗伯
I'm a managing director at Bank of New
我是新银行的董事总经理
York Mellon based in Jersey City New
约克梅隆总部设在泽西城
Jersey for those that don't know me I am
那些不认识我的人是我
the creator of a little framework called
一个小框架的创建者
Eclipse collections which means this
Eclipse集合意味着
talk will be completely unbiased also as
谈话也将完全公正
a member of the jsr 3:35 expert group
jsr 3:35专家组成员
which you know was the thing that got
你知道的是得到的东西
lambdas and streams into a Java and I've
lambda和流到Java中，我已经
been at various conferences this is my
参加过各种会议，这是我的
fourth Java one speaking I've been at
我去过的第四个Java语言
devoxx jvm language summit did so on and
devoxx jvm语言峰会这样做了，并且
so forth so yeah I'm Leonard Lima and I
等等，是的，我叫伦纳德·利马
work at Viacom it's a company I'm
我在维亚康姆公司工作
Brazilian company that does induce rely
确实引起依赖的巴西公司
or tea and I'm currently living in
或茶，我目前住在
Austin Texas
德克萨斯州奥斯汀
and I was awesome and and I am currently
而且我很棒，而且我现在
the CTO at Viacom where I let the
我让Viacom的首席技术官
software development and that's how we
软件开发，这就是我们的方式
got these talks started was they trying
他们开始尝试这些话题了
to say well you should use our framework
说得好，您应该使用我们的框架
and I said why and then you compare
我说了为什么然后你比较
collections that's how we got started
这就是我们开始的收藏
so my company's also representative at
所以我公司也是
the GCP Executive Committee and I did
GCP执行委员会，我做了
lead a GSR 363 units of measurement hi
领先GSR 363度量单位
I'm Nicole Nani Radhika I'm a vice
我是Nicole Nani Radhika我是副
president at Goldman Sachs I'm based out
我是高盛的总裁
of Salt Lake City and by academic
盐湖城和学术界
education a master's in mechanical
教育机械硕士
engineering are actually not written
工程实际上不是书面的
even HelloWorld in Java till July 3rd
甚至Java的HelloWorld截止到7月3日
2012 July 2nd 2012 was my first day at
2012 2012年7月2日是我在这里的第一天
Goldman so that's my journey starting
高盛，这就是我的旅程
March of 2017 I started owning Eclipse
2017年3月，我开始拥有Eclipse
collections the big framework which he
收集他的大框架
created so now it's pretty much my
创建，所以现在几乎是我的
responsibility to make sure I only merge
确保我只合并的责任
those things which make sense
那些有意义的事情
for the framework and that's the reason
对于框架，这就是原因
why all three of us are here because Lee
为什么我们三个都在这里，因为李
leo comes from a background where he he
狮子座来自他
does not want to use Eclipse collections
不想使用Eclipse集合
we want him to use Eclipse collections
我们希望他使用Eclipse集合
and then it ends up happening where he's
然后最终发生在他所在的地方
showing us what all things are available
向我们展示所有可用的东西
in other frameworks all right and that
在其他框架中
ends up like sort of having a nice a
最终就像有一个不错的
symbiotic relationship I should say
我应该说共生关系
where we are looking at other frameworks
我们在看其他框架
and actually comparing and that led to
并进行实际比较，从而导致
this talk yep so again my background is
是的，是的，我的背景是
you have a developer have been
你有一个开发人员
developing for 12 years more than him
比他成长12年
less than him and I've been using Java
比他少，我一直在使用Java
YouTube collections for forever and ever
永远的YouTube收藏
since they come out and so I always use
因为它们出来了，所以我总是用
it and I I don't know about you but I
它和我不了解你，但我
like my projects to have as little
像我的项目一样少
dependencies as possible it's less code
尽可能少的依赖关系
to worry about so I said well what's
担心，所以我说了什么
available on the w2 collections and and
在w2集合中可用，并且
it's been around for a while so it since
它已经存在了一段时间了
98 and with a very basic but critical
98，而且非常基础但很关键
support for collections and it has kind
对馆藏的支持，它很友善
of two main interfaces Maps and
两个主要接口Maps和
collections so there are different trees
集合，所以有不同的树
on this implementation collection this
在这个实现集合中
is everything but maps so lists at qdq
除了地图之外什么都没有，所以在qdq列出
or they are all collections and they
或是全部都是收藏品
implement in collection interface and
在收集界面中实现
maps are just Maps Cheryl the JDK
地图只是地图Cheryl JDK
provides a bunch of basic
提供了一堆基本的
implementations of these interfaces and
这些接口的实现以及
they when Java 5 came out with
他们在Java 5推出时
concurrency it they released the
并发，他们发布了
concurrent versions of them as well so
它们的并发版本也是如此
you can use them on a concurrent code
您可以在并发代码上使用它们
and they do have some algorithms for
他们确实有一些算法
doing basic stuff with all with a
做所有的基本东西
collection so like sorting shuffling
收集就像排序洗牌一样
data manipulation like adding removing
数据操作，例如添加删除
searching and all that stuff and some
搜索以及所有这些东西和一些
people are really new to the language
人们真的是新来的语言
and that's like if not the first the
这就像不是第一个
second thing you should do after hello
你好之后你应该做的第二件事
world is to work with a collection and
世界将与一个集合一起工作，
they have very good tutorials on Java
他们有关于Java的很好的教程
website on Oracle and here we have links
Oracle上的网站，这里有链接
for their simple in the concurrent
因为它们在并发中很简单
tutorials and I think I think it's very
教程，我认为我认为
nice to show how the collections
很高兴展示收藏
framework evolved since it was launched
框架自启动以来就不断发展
so that we can see where it were
这样我们就可以看到它在哪里
war and how stuff evolved over time so
战争以及事物如何随着时间演变
again um almost twenty years of
又是近二十年的
evolution and you can see that from java
演变，你可以从java中看到
to java v so from 98 to 2005 not much
到Java v，所以从98到2005并不多
has changed but then java 5 came with
已经更改，但随后Java 5附带了
generics in for loops sorry for each
for循环中的泛型对不起
loops and and that that brought that
循环，那带来了
brought a lot of improvement on code
带来了很多代码方面的改进
readability and
可读性和
doing more with your collections than
对您的收藏所做的比
you thought it was possible with the
你以为有可能
generics you didn't have to do so much
不需要太多的仿制药
casting and and they added some
铸造，他们增加了一些
concurrency utilities as well so it was
并发实用程序也是如此
a huge improvement that i saw and when i
我看到的巨大进步以及当我
when i my reason to move java 5 was
当我我搬Java 5的理由是
generics and i loved it and i stayed
仿制药，我喜欢它，我留下了
forever there it was like really good
永远在那里，真的很棒
and then on java 6 they added more a
然后在Java 6上，他们添加了更多
little bit more stuff and then java 7
一些更多的东西，然后java 7
not so much and then Java 8 was like
没那么多，然后Java 8就像
them another major overhaul so it took
他们又一次大修，所以花了
like seven years from Java to 2:05 or
例如从Java到2:05的7年，或者
more seven years in like nine years to
再过九年像九年
to get lambdas and method the references
得到lambdas并引用方法
and a bunch of other extreme interfaces
和一堆其他极端接口
which I guess you all if you didn't see
如果你没看到的话，我想你们所有人
last years in the years before Java ones
在Java之前的最后几年
there's a lot of string talks and how to
有很多弦乐话题，以及如何
use streams on this on this libraries oh
在这个库上使用流哦
sorry in these interfaces and in 2009 oh
很抱歉在这些界面中，并在2009年哦
sorry in Java 9 2017 D launched more
对不起，Java 9 2017 D启动了更多
even more stuff on the API so I saw huge
有关API的更多内容，我看到了很多
line on immutable collections for 4h
在不可变集合上排队4小时
overnight and this is something we're
一夜之间，这就是我们
gonna talk about in this talk and still
在本次演讲中将继续谈论
they are not as as wide-reaching as
他们没有像
possible and i'll show you how the needs
可能的，我会告诉你需求如何
of why i use something that is not Java
为什么我使用非Java的东西
you to collections so for example
您去收藏，例如
sometimes you're comparing things and
有时您正在比较事物，
you want to have them sorted by their
你想让他们按他们的排序
name so if you have people and have you
命名，以便如果有人和你
want to tell you how many people's are
想告诉你有多少人
with the same first-name and then you
用相同的名字，然后你
want to iterate over the people with the
想要与
same name to show their last names and
显示他们的姓氏的相同名称，以及
then we'll do a very nice table how do
然后我们将做一个非常漂亮的桌子
you do this in
你这样做
in Java you to collections you have to
在Java中，您必须要收集
have a map string of list or offset of
具有列表或偏移量的映射字符串
string again or off object and as you do
再次串起或移开物体，然后照做
these more and more and more you get a
这些越来越多，你得到一个
very long bunch of diamond operators all
非常长的钻石经营者们
around and that's really not glean and
周围真的不是很干净
another collection is you have multi map
另一个收藏是你有多张地图
that's what that's why when they said
那就是为什么当他们说
hey you should use our collections as
嘿，您应该将我们的收藏用作
well how do you guys handle multi maps I
你们如何处理多张地图
know that Apache Commons collections
知道Apache Commons集合
which is the other row library that I
这是我的另一行库
usually go to they have that and so
通常去他们那里，所以
that's how we got started talking about
这就是我们开始谈论的方式
so what are the other collections
那还有哪些其他收藏
available what what else is out there
可用那里还有什么
that people can use with Java 5 6 8 9
人们可以使用Java 5 6 8 9
that that can be used to address the
可以用来解决
collections needs and I think that's we
收藏需求，我想就是
chose for I think these are more for the
选择是因为我认为这些更适合
for more columns and we compared to Java
有关更多列，我们将其与Java进行了比较
8 collections we didn't had time slash
我们没有时间的8个收藏
experience on the Java 9 collections to
Java 9集合的经验
do a proper work of updating this
做适当的更新工作
presentation to G over 9 but Java 8
向G展示超过9，但Java 8
besides Java we have a partial comical
除了Java之外，我们还有部分漫画
actions currently on version 401 that's
当前在版本401上的操作是
what I used most outside of Java Eclipse
我在Java Eclipse以外最常使用的功能
collections that was before
之前的收藏
Goldman Sachs collections that's how
高盛的收藏就是这样
that's why Nikki was taking care of it
这就是Nikki照顾它的原因
and formerly Don was working with him
以前唐正和他一起工作
and he brought it to the open source
他把它带到了开源
which is really nice move and Google
这是非常不错的举动，而Google
guavas Google guava new offer who rather
番石榴谷歌番石榴新报价谁更
roll I didn't even know if I say it
我什至不知道我是否说
right but it was Java slang before they
是的，但是在他们之前是Java lang语
both have collections frameworks they do
都有他们做的收藏框架
other things not just collections but
其他东西不仅是收藏品
they do have certain collections so
他们确实有某些收藏品
sometimes I was using guava for
有时候我用番石榴
something else and I needed a multi map
其他的东西，我需要一张多张地图
boom there it was already you don't have
繁荣在那里已经是你没有
to bring Commons collections just for a
带来仅为一个
multi map so again we're gonna have this
多地图，所以我们再次要这个
posted and this has very good links to
发布，这有很好的链接
their user guided documentation and I
他们的用户指导文档，我
think that's one thing you have to
认为那是你必须做的一件事
consider if you're looking for something
考虑一下您是否在寻找东西
that doesn't have a good good
不好
documentation you should steer away
您应该转走的文档
because it means normally that no one is
因为这通常意味着没有人是
using
使用
and I think these guys and all these
我认为这些家伙以及所有这些
others are using a very good job in
其他人在
maintaining their documentation and I
维护他们的文件，我
think you wanna explain out is how
想你想解释的是如何
evolution I think you're the best guy to
进化我认为你是最合适的人
to talk about this so I come down here
谈论这个，所以我来这里
join you all done here
和你一起在这里完成
so if you look since you know Java 2
因此，如果您看过，因为您知道Java 2
came out and we first got the Java util
出来，我们首先得到了Java util
collections library initially in the
集合库最初位于
space she had Java collections and then
她有Java收藏的空间，然后
had Apache Commons but if you
有Apache Commons，但是如果你
fast-forward through the the last you
快进最后一个你
know almost 20 years what you see is
知道将近20年的时间
that there's a lot more stuff going on
还有更多的事情正在进行
in the collection space right and really
在收藏空间中，确实
since Java 8 coming out with the
自Java 8推出以来
addition of lambdas now there's the
现在除了lambdas
ability to do a lot more interesting
做很多有趣的事情的能力
things right and you're seeing I think a
事情对了，你看到我认为
kind of a revival in the collection
集合中的复兴
space in terms of functionality that's
就功能而言，空间
available so you know all the way you
可用，所以您一路知道
know since Java 9 has been released if
知道自从Java 9发布以来，如果
you look this year in 2017 you've got
你在2017年看起来今年
you know two new virtually three new
你知道两个新的，实际上三个新的
versions of guava you've got three new
番石榴的版本，你有三个新
versions of Eclipse collections you've
您拥有的Eclipse集合的版本
got now Java slang has become become
现在有了Java lang语已成为
Vava and you've got volver point you
瓦瓦（Vava），你有弗弗（Perver）点
know point nine and actually they're
知道第九点，实际上他们是
working on I think a current the current
我认为当前潮流
snapshot of Apache Commons you know 4.2
您知道的Apache Commons快照4.2
actually there's work actually going on
实际上有工作正在进行
there so you've seen this increase in
在那里，您已经看到这种增长
the space and two you know Leo's point
空间和两个你知道里奥的观点
there's there's a lot going on there and
那里发生了很多事，
there's a lot that of stuff that's not
有很多东西不是
available in the JDK collections today
今天在JDK集合中可用
and other you know things are providing
和其他你知道事情正在提供
those types of features so what we're
这些类型的功能，所以我们
gonna do today is actually take these
今天要去做的实际上就是
five different frameworks so Apache
五个不同的框架，所以Apache
Commons guava Eclipse collections Volvo
番石榴番石榴Eclipse系列沃尔沃
and Java eight streams and actually do a
和Java 8个流，实际上是
comparison and the domain that we're
比较和我们所处的领域
going to use during this comparison it's
在这次比较中将使用
pretty simple it's a deck of cards so we
很简单，这是一副纸牌，所以我们
have a card everybody know deck of cards
有一张卡片，每个人都知道卡片组
like playing cards if I go fish or you
喜欢玩纸牌，如果我去钓鱼或你
know solitaire or any other game so so
知道单人纸牌游戏或其他任何游戏
what do you have in the domain you have
您在域中拥有什么
and this is the common part that domains
这是领域的共同组成部分
on the bottom you have card every card
在底部，您有一张卡片
has a rank in a suit so rank is like you
穿西装有等级，所以等级就像你
know ace through ace through King and
通过国王了解王牌，
the suit is a you know spades clubs
西服是你知道的黑桃俱乐部
arts and construction of cards is pretty
艺术和纸牌构造很漂亮
simple it's actually just the Cartesian
很简单，实际上只是笛卡尔
product of those two things right and
这两个东西的乘积
it's interesting one thing I like to say
我想说的一件事很有趣
usually is you see I came down off of
通常是你看到我从
the stage it's very apropos to this
这个阶段非常适合
domain I was shuffling the collection of
我正在改组的域
speakers that we have right okay I'm
发言人，我们没事，我是
sorry
抱歉
uh-huh so anyways I digress
恩，所以我反正离题
so the problem statement we're going to
所以我们要解决的问题陈述
talk about today we have a bunch of
说说今天，我们有一堆
different operations that we're gonna
我们将要进行的不同操作
actually use and if you look in the the
实际使用，如果您查看
deck of cards itself the thing that's
一副扑克牌本身就是
going to change between the frameworks
将在框架之间进行更改
we're gonna have store the cards as an
我们将把卡片存储为
immutable list and then we're actually
不可变列表，然后我们实际上
going to group the cards into an
将卡片分组
immutable list multi map
不可变列表多图
now if framework has the types we're
现在，如果框架具有我们要的类型
going to use them if not we're going to
如果不使用它们，我们将
simulate them with the types that are
用以下类型模拟它们
available in the framework so the first
在框架中可用，因此第一个
thing we actually have to do is create
我们实际上要做的是创建
the deck of cards and I said before
牌组，我之前说过
creating a deck of cards is easy we have
创建一副扑克牌很容易
an enum of rank and an enum of suit we
一个等级枚举和一个诉讼枚举
just have to do the Cartesian product of
只需要做的笛卡尔积
those things so we're going to show you
这些东西，所以我们将向您展示
what that looks like
看起来像什么
once that's done we're gonna store it
一旦完成，我们将存储它
into an immutable list then we're gonna
进入一个不变的列表，那么我们将
group the cards into an immutable list
将卡片分组为不可变的列表
multi map then we're gonna do different
多张地图，然后我们将做不同的事情
operations we want to get the number of
我们要获取的操作数
cards by by rank and by suit and we're
卡按等级和西装划分，我们是
gonna return those either as a multi set
会把它们作为多件套归还
or bag depending on the types available
或袋子，取决于可用的类型
in the frameworks that we're using and
在我们使用的框架中
then we're gonna deal the cards now to
那我们现在要把卡片发给
deal the cards we have to shuffle them
发牌，我们必须洗牌
first and then we're gonna deal the
首先，然后我们要处理
cards out of the deck and we're going to
卡从甲板上出来，我们要
return the cards as an immutable list of
将卡片作为的不可变列表返回
assets five cards each okay so on this
资产五张，每张都可以，这样
slide what you see is what the
滑动您所看到的是什么
definition of each of the deck of cards
每副扑克牌的定义
are so once again I told you like you
再次如此，我告诉过你像你一样
have the common domain of card rank suit
具有卡片等级西装的共同领域
that doesn't change the only thing that
不会改变唯一的事情
changes is the deck of cards so we have
变化是纸牌，所以我们有
starting with JDK you see we have the
从JDK开始，您会看到
definition of JDK deck of cards we
JDK卡组的定义我们
define a list and then we have card and
定义一个列表，然后我们有卡和
then we have a map of suit to list of
然后我们有一张西装图，以列出
card right so that's what we're gonna do
卡正确，这就是我们要做的
our grouping for Apache Commons we've
我们对Apache Commons的分组
got a list of card and then petty
得到一张卡片清单，然后是零用钱
Commons actually has a multi map so
公地实际上有多张地图，所以
we're going to use the multi valued map
我们将使用多值地图
from suit to card
从西装到卡片
with the clips collections there's an
与剪辑集合，有一个
immutable list and there's an immutable
不可变的列表，并且有一个不可变的
list multi map so we're going to use
列出多张地图，以便我们使用
those types
这些类型
similarly in guava they have an
同样在番石榴，他们有一个
immutable list they have an immutable
不可变的列表，他们有一个不可变的
list multi map we're just gonna use
列出我们将要使用的多张地图
those types with Volvo we're going to
这些类型与沃尔沃，我们将
list and map there's no multi map type
列出和地图没有多地图类型
what's interesting is in the case of
有趣的是
both JDK 8 and Apache Commons you see
您看到的JDK 8和Apache Commons
with the list interface we don't have an
与列表界面，我们没有
immutable list in either of these
这两个中的不可变列表
frameworks so we have to actually we're
框架，所以我们必须实际上
gonna simulate it via unmodifiable
将通过不可修改的方式进行模拟
collections right so we're gonna
正确的收藏，所以我们要
actually create something in a rapid as
实际快速地创造出一些东西
I'm modifiable and evolve are the types
我是可修改的，进化是这种类型
that you see here list and map these are
您在这里看到的列表并映射这些是
not the JDK types so they have the same
不是JDK类型，因此它们具有相同的
name but they're actually the Vava types
名称，但实际上是Vava类型
they are immutable by default so there's
它们在默认情况下是不可变的，因此
no immutable in the name but they're
名称没有一成不变，但它们是
actually both immutable types so first
实际上这两个不可变类型，所以首先
thing we're going to do the Cartesian
我们要做笛卡尔式的事情
product so as I was working through this
产品，因为我正在研究这个
code and it's funny because we've
代码，这很有趣，因为我们已经
actually given this talk now I think
我现在实际上给出了这个演讲
this is the third conference the first
这是第三次会议第一次
two times that we gave it we used a
我们给它两次，我们使用了
completely different set of data
完全不同的数据集
structures we used a mutable sorted set
结构我们使用了可变的排序集
an immutable sorted set multi map so we
不可变的排序集多图，所以我们
wanted to try it out and see like hey if
想尝试一下，看看是否
we try change it to a mutable list what
我们尝试将其更改为可变列表
its gonna look like
它看起来像
now as I was working through solutions
现在，当我通过解决方案
on this stuff what I realized when I was
在这东西上，当我
doing the Cartesian product first thing
做笛卡尔积的第一件事
was I realized hey its Cartesian product
我意识到它的笛卡尔积
so I can you know I should actually use
所以我可以知道我应该实际使用
that and then what I realize is there's
那然后我意识到那里是
this common code that I can actually put
我可以实际输入的通用代码
in one place and share across a bunch of
在一个地方分享一堆
the solutions so what I did was on the
解决方案，所以我所做的就是
card class itself there's a stream cards
卡类本身就有一个流卡
method which I then call another method
然后我调用另一个方法的方法
on a card called Cartesian product and I
在称为笛卡尔积的卡上
take an enum set of ranks so both of
采取一个枚举等级，所以两个
these are enums so I take any number of
这些是枚举，所以我取任意数量的
the ranks enum of the set of the suits
这套西装的等级枚举
and then I actually implement Cartesian
然后我实际上实现了笛卡尔
product here so this is what a Cartesian
这里的乘积，这就是笛卡尔
product implementation looks like you
产品实施看起来像您
basically do flat map with map right
基本上用右图做平面图
once we do this when I call stream cards
当我打电话给流卡时，
I'm going to get a stream of cards out
我要拿出一堆纸牌
and then I actually have to put that
然后我实际上必须把那个
into an immutable list with Eclipse
用Eclipse变成不可变的列表
collections we actually have a Cartesian
我们实际上有一个笛卡尔坐标系
product method and actually this is a
产品方法，实际上这是一个
more recent version of that where our
我们的更新版本
old Cartesian product used to return a
用于返回一个旧的笛卡尔积
pair object right and I wanted to
配对对象正确，我想
actually make that flexible enough so I
实际上使它足够灵活，所以我
could actually return the type I wanted
实际上可以返回我想要的类型
so actually now have a Cartesian
所以实际上现在有一个笛卡尔
product that takes a function so we just
具有功能的产品，所以我们只是
use that with Eclipse collection so I
与Eclipse集合一起使用，所以我
can say like you know card new the
可以说，就像您知道卡片新
method referent or constructor
方法引用或构造函数
references are going to get mapped to a
引用将被映射到
function and then I can just call
功能，然后我可以打电话
Cartesian product here we were ordered
我们订购了笛卡尔积
so it has to go through the Mike sir
所以必须经过迈克先生
sorry sir and I think this and if she
对不起，先生，我想是这样，如果她
said like now we have it and that's
说像现在我们有它，那是
because of us as is like we were talking
因为我们就像我们在说话
and we were evolving the API and that's
我们正在开发API，那就是
what I like about open source project
我喜欢开源项目
that everyone can get started and using
每个人都可以开始使用
and it's a really good way of you
这是你的一个很好的方式
helping open-source developers is to
帮助开源开发人员
give them use cases so if I never
给他们用例，所以如果我从不
contributed one line of code to eclipse
贡献了一行代码来蚀
collections but I help them give him
收藏但我帮他们给他
like use cases and how do we do this and
例如用例，我们该如何做以及
let's move change the commentation to
让我们将注释更改为
show better how to do that so I think
更好地展示如何做到这一点，所以我认为
that's that's a really good thing that
那是一件非常好的事情
people don't normally say and you get to
人们通常不会说，你会
learn and work with people that you
与您一起学习和与他人合作
would never work together and like be
永远不会一起工作，就像
where they work in banks and I work in
他们在银行工作，而我在
IOT so has nothing to do but we are
物联网因此无关，但我们
working and learning with each other on
在彼此合作和学习
this project so I think it's really nice
这个项目，所以我认为这真的很好
and if you guys are not involved into
如果你们不参与
any open source project even just
任何开源项目，甚至只是
reading the commentation and give in
阅读评论并屈服
trying to your use case you should okay
尝试用例，你应该可以
so we're gonna well while going through
所以我们经历的时候会很好
the slides of collections compare we're
收藏集的幻灯片比较我们
not only going to compare the way the
不仅会比较
code looks like but we want to have some
代码看起来像，但是我们想要一些
metrics around it and we're going to
指标，我们将
look at two basic basic metrics one of
看两个基本的基本指标之一
the jmh metrics and the other ones are
jmh指标和其他指标是
memory tests so looking at the
内存测试，所以看
performance benchmarks it's Java micro
Java微型计算机的性能基准
harness it's it's available in the open
利用它是公开可用的
JDK and what jmh does is it you have a
JDK和jmh的作用是它有一个
few options in which you can run your
您可以在其中运行一些选项
benchmarks and you can either run it as
基准测试，您可以将其运行为
operations per second or you can run it
每秒操作数或您可以运行它
as second power operation so I mean if
作为第二次电源操作，所以我的意思是
you want to run it as operations per
您想作为每个操作运行
second you can
第二你可以
you can be rest assured that hey the
您可以放心，嘿
higher the better so basically if the
越高越好，基本上如果
number is higher that means that
数字越高，意味着
particular collection is better and it's
特定的收藏更好，它是
very important for any benchmark
对于任何基准测试都非常重要
especially a performance benchmark to
特别是性能基准
know on which machine it has run so we
知道它在哪台机器上运行，所以我们
tried to keep it on that exact same
试图保持它完全相同
machine which was my laptop and it's a
机器是我的笔记本电脑，
four core Intel i7 and we ran it with 50
四核Intel i7，我们用50跑了
warm-up iterations and 30 measurement
预热迭代和30次测量
iterations on three folks so it was
对三个人的迭代，所以
basically 90 iterations on which these
这些基本上是90次迭代
numbers are based on so the the next
数字是根据的，所以下一个
metric which you're going to look at is
您要查看的指标是
the memory test as a part of JDK 8 we
内存测试是JDK 8的一部分，我们
have an internal class in nation' called
在国家内部有一个阶级
as object size called calculator the
作为对象大小称为计算器
object size calculator gives you the
对象大小计算器为您提供
size of the complete object so if you
完整对象的大小，如果
have a list or a map then it will also
有一个列表或地图，那么它也会
have the memory of the objects or the
有对象的记忆或
elements contained inside that list so
该列表中包含的元素
part of the thing which we are doing in
我们正在做的事情的一部分
the memory test is we we take that size
内存测试是我们采用这种大小
and then we subtract the size of those
然后减去那些的大小
particular elements so that all the
特定元素，以便所有
sizes that you will see up there are of
您将看到的尺寸为
the data structure I'm right now we're
我现在的数据结构是
actually including the cards okay so
其实包括卡好吧，所以
they're using the same object so it's
他们正在使用相同的对象，所以
apples to apples comparison so for
苹果与苹果的比较因此
memory tests it's smaller numbers the
内存测试它的数字较小
better because you want to use less
更好，因为您想少用
memory and we test the size of the data
内存，我们测试数据的大小
structures created in each code example
每个代码示例中创建的结构
so looking at the actual metrics so the
因此，请查看实际指标
first one was immutable list so this was
第一个是不可变列表，所以这是
for the the group the create the deck of
为组创建甲板
cards the Cartesian products operation
卡笛卡尔积运算
so you can see in an alphabetical order
这样您就可以按字母顺序查看
from left to right you have Apache to
从左到右，您有Apache
our and all the frameworks are pretty
我们和所有框架都很漂亮
much comparable but Eclipse collections
可比性强但Eclipse集合
is about 235,000 operations per second
大约每秒235,000次操作
so it's it's slightly edging up but it's
所以它有点磨边，但是
it's not like a very significant change
这不是一个非常重大的变化
and partly one of the reasons for that
部分原因是
is whenever we create an immutable list
每当我们创建一个不可变的列表时
in Eclipse collections you have to first
在Eclipse集合中，您必须首先
go from the mutable side to the
从易变的一面走到
immutable side and let me just
不变的一面，让我
say something with these performances
用这些表演说些什么
that we're showing as well when you see
当你看到我们也在展示
something that shows 187,000 you know
显示187,000的内容
operations per second it this is
每秒的操作数
obviously not going to be in a common
显然不会有共同点
use case you're looking at you know base
您正在查看的用例知道基础
I would say base decisions for your
我会说您的基本决定
application on right that's a lot of
正确的应用程序很多
operations per second right this is all
每秒的操作数就足够了
in memory this is never likely to be a
在内存中，这永远不可能是
bottleneck for you right so the
瓶颈对吧，所以
differences they're interesting to look
差异，它们看起来很有趣
at but I wouldn't say like you know hey
在，但我不会说你知道吗
I have to use that because my code will
我必须使用它，因为我的代码将
somehow go faster this may not have any
以某种方式走得更快，这可能没有任何
impact you at all so then this is
完全影响您，所以这是
something which will definitely have an
肯定会有一个
impact on you so it's the memory use it
对你的影响，这是内存使用它
so you can see that from left to right
所以你可以从左到右看到
again it's Apache two-hour and I'll keep
再次是Apache两个小时，我会继续
on reminding that on memory side on the
提醒在记忆方面
memory test the smaller numbers the
内存测试较小的数字
better on jmh test the higher numbers
在jmh上测试更好，数字越高
the better so it's like inverse this is
更好，所以就像逆向
the memory side so the lower numbers the
内存端，所以数字越小
better you can see that Eclipse
更好的是，您可以看到Eclipse
collections and guava are pretty much at
收藏品和番石榴几乎都在
par at about at exactly at two hundred
大约等于两百
and seventy six two hundred two thousand
和76.22万
seven hundred and seventy-six bytes for
七百七十六个字节
the whole the whole deck of cards but
整个整个扑克牌，但是
the the salient point is we are not
重点是我们不是
starting at zero because we need to make
从零开始，因为我们需要
it comparable so it started at
可比性，所以它开始于
twenty-seven hundred so it's not I mean
二千七百所以不是我的意思
they are like they have an advantage but
他们就像有优势，但是
again not that big of an advantage and
再次没有太大的优势，
we'll see why in the subsequent slides
我们将在随后的幻灯片中看到原因
yes what I'm gonna do now is actually
是的，我现在要做的实际上是
show you the code that you have to write
向您展示您必须编写的代码
to do both operations doing the
做这两个操作
Cartesian product into an immutable list
笛卡尔积变成一个不变的列表
and actually then doing the group by
然后实际进行分组
first thing we're going to look at JDK
首先我们要看一下JDK
and zoom in on the code that we actually
并放大我们实际的代码
have to use just to create the immutable
必须使用仅创建不可变的
list so we're gonna do is we're going to
清单，所以我们要做的是
initialize the cards variable by calling
通过调用来初始化cards变量
card stream cards so that gives us that
卡流卡，使我们
stream of cards you know doing the
您知道的卡片流
Cartesian product and we're going to
笛卡尔积，我们将
sort it so each card actually has a it
对其进行排序，以便每张卡实际上都有一个
defines a comparator is implements
定义比较器是工具
comparable so it'll get sorted in the
可比性，因此将其排序
right order and then we can actually
正确的顺序，然后我们实际上可以
call collect and we use a collector to
叫收集，我们用收集器
list and then we're actually wrapping
清单，然后我们实际上在包装
this with a modifiable list to make it
这个带有可修改的列表
effectively immutable what's interesting
有效地改变了有趣的事情
is I've tried this a number of different
是我尝试了许多不同的方法
ways you can actually try and use like
您可以实际尝试和使用的方式
collectors with collecting and then and
收藏家与收集，然后
it works and actually looks kind of more
它可以工作，实际上看起来更多
fluent but it actually winds up being a
流利，但实际上成为
little bit Messier on the screen so I
屏幕上有点梅西耶，所以我
went with basically the simplest thing I
基本上是我最简单的事情
could show here which was actually doing
可以在这里显示实际在做什么
the wrapping on the outside with Apache
用Apache在外面包裹
Commons
公地
collections similarly we're going to use
类似地，我们将要使用的集合
the stream cards and I'll zoom in and
流卡，然后我将放大
sort them and we use the same collectors
对它们进行排序，我们使用相同的收集器
to list from the gatk
从盖特清单中列出
patchy Commons has a classical list
斑驳的下议院有一个经典清单
utils and we're going to call this
utils，我们将其称为
details on modifiable list to actually
实际可修改列表上的详细信息
wrap wrap the list to get you know
包裹包裹清单，让您知道
pseudo immutability with the clips
剪辑的伪不变性
collections a set of calling stream
收集一组呼叫流
cards are now going to call lazy cards
卡现在将称为懒卡
so lazy cards gives us a lazy iterable
所以懒牌给我们一个懒惰的迭代
and then what we can do on that is use
然后我们可以做的就是使用
the API for two sorted lists so we've
两个排序列表的API，所以我们已经
now got a sorted list that's mutable and
现在有一个可变的排序列表，
we call two immutable and now we have an
我们称两个不可变，现在我们有一个
immutable list getting stored into cards
不变列表存储到卡中
with guava if we zoom in we get the
用番石榴，如果我们放大我们得到
stream cards we then call sorted on the
然后我们将流卡称为“
stream and then there's a special
流，然后有一个特殊的
collector that guava gives you on a
番石榴给你的收藏家
mutable list the class there's actually
可变列出实际存在的班级
two immutable lists so you can do sorted
两个不可变列表，因此您可以进行排序
dot collect and then you know passing a
点收集，然后您知道通过了
mutable list to to a mutable list with
可变列表到可变列表
Vava we zoom in we're taking the same
静脉，我们放大，我们采取相同
stream cards and then we call sort it
流卡，然后我们将其排序
again and then Vava also has its own
再次，瓦瓦也有自己的
collector on its list class which can
在其列表类上的收集器可以
call list collector and that actually
电话清单收集器，实际上
gives you the immutable list okay so
给你不可变的清单好吧
that was how we create the immutable
那就是我们创造不变的方式
list right pretty simple
列出权利非常简单
okay next thing we're going to do is
好，接下来我们要做的是
group the cards by suit in an immutable
将衣服按西装分组成一成不变
list multi map so first I want to
列出多张地图，所以首先我想
explain what exactly a multi map is so
解释到底什么是多重地图
like Leo mentioned before a party hard
就像利奥在聚会前提到的那样
it's multi maps and everything so
这是多张地图，一切如此
basically a multi map is a multivalued
基本上，多图是多值的
map so it's gonna have one key and it's
地图，所以它会有一把钥匙，
gonna have a collection of values a
将有一个价值观的集合
normal map is gonna have one key and one
法线贴图将有一把钥匙和一把
values one value but a multi map is
值一个值，但多图是
where it has multiple values or there by
它有多个值或在那里
the name so if you look at the group by
名称，所以如果您查看分组依据
operations
运作
you can see that to get a particular
你可以看到得到一个特定的
multi map you're essentially grouping by
您实质上是按照多地图分组
the key that's why we're mentioning this
这就是为什么我们要提到这个的关键
to be a group by and you can see that in
成为一个小组，你可以看到
a performance test the higher the better
性能测试越高越好
so you can see that wah-wah is oh sorry
所以你可以看到哇哇，对不起
the JDK is the clear winner and partly
JDK无疑是赢家，部分原因是
the reason for that is JDK does not have
原因是JDK没有
an immutable multi map so and we will
一个不变的多图，所以我们将
see much more in in detail in the in the
在中详细了解更多
codecs whereas as opposed to the Eclipse
编解码器，而与Eclipse相反
collections as well as guava have their
收集和番石榴都有
multi Maps so does I think so so does
多地图我也这样认为
Apache and if you see again the the the
Apache，如果您再次看到
performance metrics are like JDK blows
性能指标就像是JDK的打击
through the charts I mean they pretty
通过图表，我的意思是他们很漂亮
much just go through it and that's
很多只是通过它，那就是
partly the reason because of the
部分原因是由于
immutability aspect of it but if you
它的不变性，但是如果你
compare with the actual space used then
然后与实际使用的空间进行比较
again all the frameworks are pretty much
同样，所有框架都差不多
compatible so all I'm trying to say out
兼容，所以我想说出来
here is if you're looking for an
如果您正在寻找
immutable a really really immutable
一成不变的
multi map then you have to be cognizant
多图，那么你必须要认识
about both besides the performance as
除了性能
well as the memory to memory side on the
以及内存到内存端
memory side it's pretty much comparable
内存方面几乎是可比的
out there for okay so now we're gonna
在那里可以，所以现在我们要
focus on what the group by code looks
专注于按代码分组的外观
like right so once again we're trying to
就像是正确的，所以我们再次尝试
create an immutable list multi map and
创建一个不可变的列表多图并
since we don't have that type available
因为我们没有可用的类型
in the JDK
在JDK中
we have to make sure that when we create
我们必须确保在创建时
the map with the lists that the map is
带有列表的地图
both unmodifiable and the lists are
都是不可修改的，列表是
unmodifiable right so we take we take
不可修改的权利，所以我们采取
the cards we then and you can see we're
然后我们可以看到的卡片
using the collectors collecting and then
用收集者收集，然后
here so we do a grouping by we group by
在这里，我们进行分组
suit and then we map you know based on
西装，然后我们根据您知道的地图
identity and have to do collectors
身份和要做收藏家
collecting and then create the list and
收集然后创建列表，并
actually make sure that each individual
实际上要确保每个人
list inside gets wrapped in a none
里面的清单被包裹在一个无
modifiable list and then that final
可修改的列表，然后是最终的
collecting and then this is where I told
收集，然后这就是我告诉的地方
you before I use that remember I used
你在我使用之前记得我曾经
collectors unmodifiable arts art
收藏家不可修改的艺术
collections that I'm not a fiber list I
我不是纤维清单的收藏
could have done that with unmodifiable
本来可以修改的
map but I wanted to show you like this
地图，但我想给你看
is what
是什么
collecting and then looks like right so
收集然后看起来像是正确的
you got those two options either I could
我有两个选择
have wrapped the whole thing in a call
把整个事情都包裹在一个电话里
to collections done find a file map or I
到收藏完成找到文件映射或我
can use the collecting in them which
可以在其中使用收集
does it as well
也一样
and I could have zoomed in here but it's
我本可以放大这里的，但是
funny because on this page it doesn't
有趣，因为在此页面上没有
actually get you know much bigger on the
实际上让您知道更多
slides it doesn't really help with
幻灯片并没有真正帮助
Apache collections what we actually get
Apache收集我们实际得到的东西
to do is we create a yes we're gonna go
我们要做的是创建一个是的，我们要去
back okay we got a stream of cards first
回来好吧，我们首先得到了卡片流
thing we had to do is say collecting in
我们要做的就是说收集
them which means we're going to collect
他们，这意味着我们要收集
something and then we're going to do
一些事情，然后我们将要做
something to it after we collect it
收集到东西之后
right that thing that what we're going
正确的事情，我们要去
to do is first we're gonna do a group by
首先要做的是
right so we're effectively going to
对，所以我们实际上将
create a map of you know lists the keys
创建一个您知道的列表钥匙
in the map are going to be the suits
在地图上将会很适合
lists are gonna be the cards for that
清单将是为此的卡片
suit and what we're gonna make sure is
西装，我们要确定的是
that when we're collecting up those
当我们收集那些
lists yes and the face that you're
列出是和你的脸
making is exactly the face you should be
正是你应该做的脸
making he likes to be responsive this
让他喜欢对此做出回应
slide yeah so the the point is they make
滑动是的，所以重点是
to me is that this is long and is is
对我来说，这很长，而且是
hiding some some implementation or
隐藏一些实现或
characteristics from the interface or
界面的特性或
actually the other way around it's
实际上，相反的方法是
exposing stuff there so it's not really
在那里暴露东西，所以不是真的
beautiful I like because even though you
我喜欢美丽，因为即使你
have a mood a modifiable list you get a
有一个可修改的清单，你会得到一个
list that has an ADD method yeah you
有ADD方法的列表，是的，您
don't want to return a non-modifiable
不想返回不可修改的
map that has mutable lists in it right
右边有可变列表的地图
because then it's really not immutable
因为那真的不是一成不变的
right yeah really complicated to do like
是的，做起来真的很复杂
this is the case where because you don't
这是因为你不这样做
have a data structure and you try and do
有一个数据结构，你尝试去做
things through algorithms it becomes
通过算法将事物变成
more complicated right it would have
更复杂的权利
been better served via data structure
通过数据结构得到更好的服务
and one more thing to add about the
还有一件关于
unmodifiable aspect of it is whenever
不可修改的方面是
you are doing something unmodifiable
你正在做一些不可修改的事情
versus immutable it's different if
与不可变相比，如果
you're going from an from a mutable side
你是从一个易变的一面走
to the immutable side then that's always
到不变的一面，那总是
an O in operation because you have to
运行中的O，因为您必须
make sure you have a copy of the
确保您有一份
immutable because an immutable list or
不可变的，因为不可变的列表或
an immutable collection is has to
一个不可变的集合是必须
maintain its state all over the place as
在整个地方保持其状态
opposed to unmodifiable where you just
反对你无法修改的地方
add a wrapper on it and then all it's
在上面添加一个包装，然后全部
going to do is for all mutating
要做的就是所有变异
operation it's going to go and throw
操作将要抛出
grunting so you're comparing oh one
咕unt一声，所以您正在比较哦
versus Oh n and that clearly shows in
与哦n，这清楚地表明
the performance benchmarks
性能基准
okay so fast forwarding to Apache common
好的，所以可以快速转发到Apache
so they do have a data structure here
所以他们这里确实有数据结构
right and it's interesting because the
对，这很有趣，因为
list valued map that we created here
列出我们在此处创建的有价值的地图
using multi map utils is a mutable multi
使用multi map utils是可变的
map and then we iterate over the cards
映射，然后我们遍历卡片
just using for each calling put into the
只是用于输入的每个呼叫
multi map so put on a multi map has the
多图，因此放在多图上具有
effect of finding the key in the multi
在多重中找到密钥的效果
map and basically adding to the list
映射并基本上添加到列表中
that's at that key but then there's a
那是关键，但是有一个
utility class and Apache Commons called
实用程序类和称为Apache Commons的
multi map utils and we can actually wrap
多地图实用程序，我们实际上可以包装
the whole multi map in and unmodifiable
整个多图，不可修改
you know multi value map which is a
你知道多值地图是
little bit less complex than what we had
比我们所拥有的要简单一些
before still taking something that's
还是拿些东西之前
model you know mutable and then making
您知道可变的模型，然后制作
it immutable at the end so the clips
最后它是不可变的，所以剪辑
collections since we have an API for
集合，因为我们有一个API
group by and since all of our methods
由于我们所有的方法
are covariant we on an immutable list a
是协变量，我们在一个不变的列表上
group by will we return an immutable
我们将返回一个不变的
list multi map so we just have to say
列出多张地图，所以我们只需要说
cards group by card get suit we get back
卡片组逐个穿衣服，我们回来了
the immutable list multi map do you want
您想要的不可变列表多地图
me to explain this that's like the
我来解释这就像
selling points like you its if you need
像你这样卖点
something that it's not there we put it
有些东西不在那里，我们把它
there and then use it and reuse it
在那里然后使用它并重复使用
please remember this was this was faster
请记住，这是更快
this was faster I ran you last time this
这是我上次跑给你的更快
was slower but it wasn't slower for me
慢一点，但对我来说却不慢
to write right yeah okay Google guava so
写正确是的，好的，谷歌番石榴，所以
in guava there's a class called multi
番石榴里有一类叫多
maps which has an index and this returns
具有索引的地图，此地图返回
a very specific size and this is the
一个非常具体的尺寸，这是
downside of using static utility you can
使用静态实用程序的缺点是您可以
only return one type out of here our
只从这里返回一种类型
group by is covariant so it's based on
group by是协变的，因此它基于
the type you're eating over index always
你总是在索引上进食的类型
returns a mutable list multi map but it
返回可变列表多图，但它
works well here so I can use multi maps
在这里效果很好，所以我可以使用多张地图
index takes an iterable which we just
索引需要迭代
passed in cards and then we do card suit
传递卡片，然后做卡片套装
and it's nice and simple and it is
它既好又简单，它是
amitabh alyssum all team up with Volvo
amitabh alyssum全部与沃尔沃合作
similar to eclipse collections bobbers
类似于eclipse collection bobbers
group by actually returns an immutable
分组依据实际上返回一个不可变的
map it's not a multi map but gives us
地图不是多张地图，而是给了我们
the same effect so I can just say cards
同样的效果，所以我只能说卡片
group by card get suit so in the
依卡分组适合
interest of time
时间的利益
is gonna breeze through this one because
会轻而易举地通过这个，因为
this is like one one shot where you're
这就像一枪一击
seeing on the left is the deck of cards
在左边看到的是纸牌
so that's actually when you sort of
所以实际上是当你
superimpose do some math you end of the
叠加做一些数学
two things on the right you'll get that
在右边的两件事，你会得到
but no we actually ran the test so
但是不，我们实际上进行了测试，所以
there's no math involved in there it's
那里没有数学
what the the actual performance tests
实际的性能测试是什么
look like so you can see that all of
看起来像这样，您可以看到所有
them on the left to create a deck of
他们在左边创建一个甲板
card is the sum total is same all right
卡总和是可以的
but if you look at the immutable list
但是如果你看一眼不可变的清单
and the group when I say same it's
当我说相同的时候
similar if you look at immutable list
如果您看一眼不可变的列表，则类似
and group by however the JDK is breezing
和分组，但JDK轻而易举
through but it gets compensated because
通过但它得到补偿，因为
of the immutable list again you're
再次出现在不可变列表中
looking at modifiable versus immutable
看着可修改与不变
so keep that in mind it's Oh n vs o one
所以请记住，这是一个
and we're gonna again the memory is
我们会再次回忆
comparable and one of the reasons why
可比性，也是原因之一
our has the highest memory usages
我们的内存使用率最高
because of the way they're immutable
因为它们是不可变的
lists are implemented because they're
实施列表是因为它们
linked lists at underneath the covers
封面下方的链接列表
yeah now obviously these numbers aren't
是的，现在显然这些数字不是
interesting from your application
您的应用程序很有趣
perspective but if you consider the deck
角度，但如果您考虑甲板
of cards as maybe something that would
的卡片，也许会
be represented in your domain maybe you
在您的域中代表您
know customer order and you've had
知道客户的订单，你已经
millions of those things right what you
数以百万计的这些事情对您有用
can see then is that you know what is
可以看到的是，你知道什么是
now measured in bytes on these slides
现在在这些幻灯片上以字节为单位
could be measured in either megabytes or
可以以兆字节或
you know if yet enough of them could be
你知道他们是否足够
a you know who knows gigabytes right
一个你知道谁知道千兆字节的权利
okay next thing we're gonna do is get
好吧，我们要做的下一件事就是
the number of cards so there should be a
卡的数量，所以应该有一个
little bit easier we're gonna count by
我们会轻松一点
suit and count by rank so we have the
西装和按等级计数，所以我们有
basic concept called as a multi set or a
基本概念称为多集或
bag so what that means is if you have
袋子，那意味着如果你有
one element then how many of those
一个元素然后那么几个
elements are are there in that
元素在那里
particular collection so for Eclipse
Eclipse的特定集合
collections we have something called as
集合中我们有一个叫做
a bag a patch a has a multi set and the
一袋一个补丁有一个多套和
bag
袋
they're basically the same thing Wow
他们基本上是一样的东西
guava has a multi set though the
番石榴虽然有多种设置
difference between each of these is our
这些之间的差异是我们的
bag is actually implemented underneath
包实际上是在下面实现的
the covers as a primitive map so it's an
作为原始地图的封面，所以它是
object in map and if you look at the
地图中的对象，如果您查看
that's that's one of the reasons why the
这就是为什么
the way we created we pretty much are
我们创造的方式几乎是
really fast but that's really really
真的很快，但是那真的
significant or it's apparent when you
重要的，或者当你
see the memory test now these are
现在看内存测试，这些是
starting at zero okay so for the whole
从零开始，所以整个
guns by suit for all our suits which are
我们所有的西服套装
there you end up getting the memory
在那里你最终得到了记忆
consumption to be just 408 bytes for
消耗仅为408字节
eclipse collections and the JDK and
eclipse集合以及JDK和
wahwah are at par and Apache and guava
wahwah的水准与Apache和guava相同
are pretty much at par as well then
那时也差不多
counts by rank so again same thing
依等级计算同样是一回事
underneath it's the multi set and the
在下面是多集和
back difference but the difference
后背差异，但差异
between counts by suit and count by rank
在按西装数和按等级数之间
are the number of keys that you will
您将要使用的键数
have so that ends up impacting the
因此最终会影响
performance test and more so it it is
性能测试等等
very apparent on the memory test but
在内存测试中非常明显，但是
again because Eclipse callenge Eclipse
再次因为Eclipse callenge Eclipse
collections is bags are underneath an
收藏是袋子在下面
object in trap we end up saving the most
陷阱中的对象我们最终节省了最多
memory okay so I want to serve the code
内存还可以，所以我想提供代码
for these you know performance stats and
对于这些，您知道性能统计信息和
what you see is if we want to count by
您看到的是我们是否要依靠
suit count by rank with the JDK what we
用JDK按等级排序，我们
do is we take the cards we called that
我们是拿走了我们称为的卡片
stream we're then gonna call the collect
流，然后我们将称为收集
method on stream and use collectors
流中的方法并使用收集器
grouping by collectors counting and
按收藏家分组，计数和
we've seen this code before well that's
我们之前已经看过了这段代码
the first time okay this is Oh Maurice
第一次好吧，这是哦莫里斯
you've seen this code before you've
您之前已经看过此代码
probably given you know this code in
可能是因为您知道此代码在
talks before right maybe not with cards
没事就没事说话
so anyways this is how you actually you
所以反正这就是你实际上的方式
know count something right if you want
知道算什么，如果你想
to count them by a particular key so
用一个特定的键来计算它们
here we're coming the cards by the suit
这是西装的卡片
and we get back a map of suit too long
我们回来的西装图太久了
right
对
same thing for kind of a rank we still
同样的事情，我们仍然排名
call the stream collect collectors
调用流收集收集器
grouping by use the different key we're
通过使用不同的键分组
gonna use card get rank and then
将使用卡获得等级，然后
collectors counting with Apache
用Apache计数的收藏家
collections kind of interesting Apache
集合类型有趣的Apache
collections has both the bag and a
集合既有手提袋又有一个
multiset they are the same thing right
多集他们是同一回事
just two different names it historically
历史上只有两个不同的名称
had bagged multi stet was introduced
引入袋装式多行程
more recent I think since versions four
我认为是自第四版以来
so it's kind of surprised to find it so
所以发现它有点惊讶
in this case I used both because they
在这种情况下，我使用这两个都是因为
were both there hey you know I like one
都在那嘿，你知道我喜欢一个
I like the other I like both
我喜欢另一个
right so what we're doing though here as
对，所以我们在做什么
we stream we then map the attribute
我们流我们然后映射属性
either gets suit or get rank and then we
要么获得诉讼或获得排名，然后我们
collect into the target collection
收集到目标集合中
either the hash bag or the hash multiset
哈希包或哈希多集
this is going to have the effect as
这将产生如下效果
we're adding into a hash multicenter bag
我们将添加到一个哈希多中心包中
the the data structure itself keeps
数据结构本身保持
track of the counts internally so we
在内部跟踪计数，因此我们
don't actually have to specify the
实际上不必指定
algorithm like we did with collectors
像我们对收集器所做的算法
grouping by collectors counting with the
按收藏家分组
clips collections and this is a new API
剪辑集合，这是一个新的API
into the LEAs point before it you know
进入LEA点之前
as I was writing these you know this
当我写这些的时候，你知道这一点
talk for dev ox I was like seeing I was
为dev ox说话我就像看到我是
like you know I'd really be nice if we
就像你知道，如果我们
had a method called count buy because
有一种叫做计数购买的方法，因为
when I show people that you have to use
当我告诉别人你必须使用
as lazy collect back to bag what's as
懒得回去收拾包
lazy what's collecting what's to bag
懒惰正在收集什么书包
right it doesn't make a lot of sense if
对，如果没有太大的意义
you don't know what these things are and
你不知道这些是什么
I have to explain them to you
我要跟你解释一下
but I can show you mat the count by and
但我可以告诉您
that actually probably conveys a little
实际上可能传达了一些
bit more meaning as to what's happening
关于正在发生的事情的更多含义
here just a little so we call this stuff
这里只是一点，所以我们称这个东西
cards count by and specify what we want
卡计数并指定我们想要的
to count by and we get back a bag of
算数，我们拿回一袋
soup now you may still ask about well
汤，现在您可能仍然会问得很好
what's a bag and you can imagine
什么是包包，你可以想象
underneath a bag is a basically map of
袋子下面是一张基本上的地图
suit to sum count or in this case in the
适合求和或在这种情况下
other case bag of rank map of rank to
等级图的其他案例包
sum count guava has a multiset they do
番石榴总和他们有一个多集
not I've also have bags so I only use
不，我也有包，所以我只用
multi sub but here same thing I did with
多子，但在这里我做了同样的事情
a patch of Commons I ate over the cards
我在卡片上吃过一块下议院
using stream and I collect and guava has
使用流，我收集和番石榴有
this collector on a class called multi
这个收集器在一个叫做multi的类上
set so and it's interesting this is one
设置为如此，有趣的是，这是一个
of the things that as a as the creator
作为创造者的事物
of a collections framework it's kind of
收集框架的一种
interesting to put on a someone else's
穿上别人的衣服很有趣
pair of shoes and go into their
一双鞋，进入他们的
collections framework and try and
收集框架并尝试
discover how to use it and it actually
发现如何使用它，实际上
helps you develop a little bit more
帮助您多一点发展
sympathy and empathy to developers who
对开发人员的同情和同情
have to try and discover your API right
必须尝试发现您的API正确
it's like how do you find this stuff and
就像您如何找到这些东西，
where's the documentation and oh my gosh
文件在哪里，哦，天哪
like nothing's of Allah it's too hard
像真主一样，这太难了
how can I give up
我怎么能放弃
so anyways I discovered Maltese that's
所以无论如何我发现马耳他语是
existed and you can do collect you know
存在，你可以收集你知道的
into multi sets to multi set you specify
分成多组到指定的多组
what you want to effectively count by
您想要有效地计算的依据
and you can actually here specify a
您实际上可以在此处指定一个
count function as well so I'm just
也算功能，所以我只是
mapping the element to one I'm counting
将元素映射到我正在计数的元素
by ones and then into hash multi set
逐个然后放入哈希多集
Evolver was interesting barber doesn't
Evolver很有趣，理发师没有
have a bag or a multiset and it didn't
有一个袋子或多件套，但没有
really have a good way for me to also do
对我来说真的有一个很好的方法
the work in their own maps so I
在自己的地图上工作，所以我
basically just delegated out to using a
基本上只是委派使用
Java util map now it's interesting you
Java util map现在很有趣
see the problem here in that I was
在这里看到的问题是
coding it in a class where I had a map
在我有地图的课程中编码
that was Volvos on a map that was java's
那是沃尔沃斯在Java的地图上
and now I have to basically solve the
现在我必须基本解决
problem of two things with the same name
两件事同名的问题
and I have to use packages in the names
我必须使用名称中的包
on the on these methods but guava
在这些方法上，但番石榴
I'm sorry Vava has a method called
抱歉，瓦瓦（Vava）有一个方法
collect directly on their type and what
直接收集它们的类型和内容
it is it's a shortcut to get to stream
这是流媒体的捷径
collect so they give you basically a
收集，所以他们基本上给你一个
shortcut to that right so you know I
右边的快捷方式，所以你知道我
don't know if this day this knock card
不知道这天这张敲门卡
is that stream collect I can just say
是我只能说的流收集
this card's collect pass in a collector
此卡的收集通行证在收集器中
I'm doing the grouping by counting and
我正在通过计数来分组
this is effectively the same thing that
这实际上是同一件事
the JDK and Apache Commons did and now
JDK和Apache Commons做到了，现在
we're gonna deal some cards do you want
我们要发一些卡吗
to skip this slide we've just four six
跳过这张幻灯片，我们只有四个六
minutes ago okay
分钟前还可以
dealing cards is fast okay so when we
发卡很快，所以当我们
deal cards what we're gonna do is return
发卡，我们要做的就是退货
an immutable list of sets of five each
一组不可变的列表，每组五个
and what you see here is we're gonna
你在这里看到的是我们要
take a stack and in the JDK case we're
拿一个堆栈，在JDK的情况下
using the recommendation for a stack we
使用推荐的堆栈，我们
actually use a deck loser a deck we're
实际使用失败者
gonna pass in that deck the number of
要传递的甲板数量
hands that we want and the cards per
我们想要的手和每张卡片
hand and we're gonna use create an
手，我们将使用创建一个
unmodifiable list wrapped around calling
不可修改的清单环绕着通话
in stream range map to object we're
在流范围内映射到对象
basically this is going to give us the
基本上这将给我们
hand each of the hands so we get the set
交出每只手，这样我们就得到了一套
and then we're gonna actually then
然后我们实际上会
return that as the list wrap doesn't I
返回，因为列表包装不是
modify the list it's a mouthful by the
修改列表，
way all this code is available online
所有这些代码都可以在线获得的方式
and you can go see it and try it
你可以去看看并尝试
yourself as well we'll have it at the
您自己也可以在
link at the end for Apache it's pretty
Apache末尾的链接很漂亮
much the same except for that list utils
除了清单utils以外，其他基本相同
thing right with codes collections we
正确的代码集合，我们
have instead of int stream we have our
有而不是int流，我们有
own into interval I do one two hand so
自己进入间隔我做一只两只手，所以
this is the number of hands I want it's
这是我想要的手数
one two five then collect up the the
一二五然后收集
sets of hands that I want so
我想要的套手
this deal returns a set and then because
这笔交易返回一组，然后因为
we are collecting over what some
我们正在收集一些
effective Liana mutable int list in the
有效的Liana可变int列表
case of interval that actually winds up
间隔实际上结束的情况
returning and immutable list
返回且不变的列表
automatically with guava similar to the
用番石榴自动类似于
JDK an Apache except for we use a
JDK和Apache，除了我们使用
different collector we're gonna collect
我们要收集的其他收集者
into the immutable list at the end and
进入不可变列表的最后，
then bobber that's I'm trying it's
然后浮子就是我在尝试
interesting bothersome types are by
有趣的麻烦类型是
default immutable and what you see here
默认不可变以及您在此处看到的内容
is they actually have an immutable stack
他们实际上有一个不变的堆栈
and I think actually a bug on our slides
我认为实际上是我们幻灯片上的错误
here I should actually change that it
在这里我应该改变它
used to be called stack in Java slang
过去在Java lang语中被称为堆栈
and it has changed to just be list so
它已更改为仅列出
--lifts it's immutable and what it means
-提升它的一成不变及其含义
is we can't actually change it so
是我们实际上无法更改它吗
imagine you have an immutable stack
想象你有一个不变的堆栈
right how do you push and pop to it well
正确，如何将其推入并弹出
every time you do an operation on it
每次您对其进行操作时
you're gonna have to get a new stack and
你将不得不获得一个新的堆栈，
the thing that you've popped off right
你突然冒出来的东西
and that's what you see is actually
这就是你所看到的
happening here every time we do
我们每次都在这里发生
something we get back a couple two of
我们回到了两个
the thing that we wanted and you know
我们想要的东西，你知道
then we have to keep you know passing in
那么我们必须让您知道传承
a new copy of the stack effectively
有效地复制堆栈的新副本
right so this was kind of hard to reason
是的，所以这很难推理
about it first and to think it's like I
首先考虑它，就像我一样
just wanted an immutable stack I mean
我只想要一个不变的堆栈
are mutable stack but uh you know I used
堆栈是可变的，但是你知道我用过
what they had available
他们有什么
yes yes I did that is not that is not my
是的，我做到了那不是那不是我的
code so to repeat the question the
代码，以便重复该问题
question was do they have methods with
问题是他们是否有方法
underscore in their name yes so topple
用他们的名字强调是的
to does have an underscore one and
确实有一个下划线
underscore two we have we also have like
强调两个我们有我们也有喜欢
a pair we just call it get one get two
我们称之为一对一对
but that's a naming convention so they
但这是一个命名约定，所以他们
went with underscore one so okay with
强调了一个这样的
that
那
we have this comparison table so what
我们有这个比较表
everybody wants to know is like what's
每个人都想知道就像什么
the best framework for me right and of
对我来说最好的框架
course the answer is well that depends
当然答案取决于
what are you looking for right and what
您在找什么，什么
you see is that we tried to weigh things
你看到的是我们试图权衡事物
across the frameworks based on features
跨框架基于功能
that we were thought were interesting
认为我们很有趣
and then we tried to rank what we
然后我们尝试对我们的排名
thought were for each of those features
以为是每个功能
the top three so if all you need are
前三名，所以如果您需要的是
lists set and map JDK is great use it
列表集和地图JDK很好用
what what do you need anything for right
您需要什么才对
it's got a lot of functionality
它有很多功能
especially now with streams if you need
尤其是现在，如果需要，可以使用流
bags and multi maps and buy maps well
箱包和多张地图，很好地购买地图
there are frameworks available that can
有可用的框架可以
give you those right so you've got a
给你那些权利，所以你有一个
patch you've got guava you know you've
你有番石榴的补丁，你知道你有
got Eclipse with those things you need
Eclipse提供了您需要的那些东西
the stack
堆栈
well you can they use deck if you want
好吧，如果需要，他们可以使用甲板
or you know you can use immutable stacks
或者你知道你可以使用不可变的堆栈
from bravura or you can use mutable
从bravura或您可以使用可变
stacks from Eclipse collections any
Eclipse集合中的任何堆栈
trees or tries or tables you know these
你知道这些的树或尝试或表
are available and you know you know
有空，你知道你知道
certain frameworks not available across
某些跨框架不可用的框架
the others but if you need things like
其他的，但是如果你需要像
immutables and you know primitives and a
不可变的，你知道基元和
really fluent api it really once again
真的很流利的API
depends on what you're looking for and
取决于您要寻找的东西
you can kind of see like you know what's
你可以看到自己知道是什么
available we've kind of ranked we've got
可用，我们已经获得了一定的排名
green checkmarks for yes red Xs for no
绿色复选标记为是，红色Xs为否
and then green checkmarks and boxes for
然后是绿色的复选标记和框
kind of and then the you know orange x's
一种，然后您知道橙色x
and the boxes for not really right so
和盒子不是很正确，所以
for state check boxes those are awesome
对于状态复选框，那些很棒
right alright so anyways that's a kind
好吧，反正这是一种
of the talk week a stick some quick
谈话周的时间比较快
questions but here's the link to the
问题，但这是指向
source code it's going to check it out
源代码将要签出
and there's multiple implementations out
并且有多种实现
there there's the immutable sorted set
有不变的排序集
implementation which we used in our dev
我们在开发人员中使用的实现
ox talk and the immutable list one which
牛话和不可变的清单之一
we've done today
我们今天完成了
kind of see like what the code looks
看起来像代码的样子
like and you know I would experience you
喜欢，你知道我会经历你
know say experiment for yourself the
知道自己说实验
things out there try it for yourself try
那里的东西自己尝试一下
different data types if you want to
如果您想要不同的数据类型
measure it if the performance is
如果性能是
interesting to you you know you can use
对您很有趣，您知道您可以使用
the the jmh benchmarks and you can use
jmh基准，您可以使用
the Nass horn you know object size
知道物体大小的纳斯角
calculator if you're curious what the
计算器，如果您好奇什么
memory footprint of something is yeah so
是的东西的内存占用量是这样的
including our performance benchmarks our
包括我们的性能基准
memory tests everything is out on the
内存测试一切都在
tree people will be pushing these slides
树人将推这些幻灯片
out on the Java one speaker deck as well
在Java上也是如此
so they would be made available as well
因此它们也将可用
along with that we might put them on
以及我们可能会把它们放在
SlideShare but if you have any questions
SlideShare，但是如果您有任何疑问
I mean I know we are almost out of time
我的意思是我知道我们快没时间了
if you have any questions you can always
如果您有任何疑问，您可以随时
tweet to any one of us and we will start
向我们任何人发推文，我们将开始
redirecting who is an expert in which
重定向谁是专家
collection or in which framework so to
集合或在哪个框架中
say and we will be here at JavaOne
说，我们将在JavaOne
downstairs and the developers lounge
楼下和开发商休息室
area as well as tomorrow around there so
地区以及周围的明天，所以
if you have any questions you can just
如果您有任何疑问，您可以
tackle us and we'll we can talk more
解决我们，我们会谈更多
offline and I think you know I like to
离线，我想你知道我喜欢
echo what Leo said before as well right
呼应狮子座之前所说的话
all of these frameworks are open-source
所有这些框架都是开源的
if you're going to use them and you like
如果您要使用它们，并且您喜欢
them you know as someone who you know
他们你认识的人
maintains an open-source framework I
维护一个开源框架
love when people contribute the things
当人们贡献事物时热爱
that they need right yes it'd be great
他们需要正确的，是的，这很棒
if I built everything that you needed
如果我建立了您需要的一切
for you I've built most of what I needed
为您打造了我所需的大部分东西
but if you have you need something to be
但是如果你有，你需要做些什么
great you know really appreciate
太棒了，您知道的非常感谢
contribution and we're here to help you
贡献，我们在这里为您提供帮助
do that right it's like you want to do
做到这一点就像你想做的那样
that we can help you you know in github
我们可以在github中为您提供帮助
you know in terms of doing the coding
你知道在编码方面
getting code reviews and actually
得到代码审查，实际上
getting your contributions merged into
将您的贡献合并到
the repos and contribution is not just
回购和贡献不只是
by code if you find a bug or if you want
如果发现错误或想要通过代码
a feature please do request us because
功能请要求我们，因为
for Eclipse collections 9.0 we had a ton
对于Eclipse Collections 9.0，我们有很多
of user requests which we ended up
最终导致的用户请求数量
accommodating and uses other than done
容纳和使用以外的用途
so we so we we do look at that and and
所以我们如此，我们确实要研究和
we like it when our users tell us to
当我们的用户告诉我们
improve the framework because that's the
改进框架，因为那是
we can't reach the whole spectrum of our
我们无法达到我们的全部范围
own code and do not forget to vote I'm
自己的代码，不要忘记投票我
totally fine if you were down with us
如果你和我们在一起就很好
but just come back and tell us why
但只要回来告诉我们为什么
you're down voting because it will help
您不赞成投票，因为这会有所帮助
us improve our next stop yes again we
我们改善我们的下一站是
won't take it personally
不会亲自考虑
don't worry about it and thanks
不用担心，谢谢
everybody for attending how great Java 1
每个人都参加了Java 1的出色表现
yeah
是的
you
您